https://saint-therese.org/privacy-policy-terms-of-use/

Privacy Policy & Terms of Use - National Shrine and Museum of St. Therese
Skip to main content Skip to footerNational Shrine and Museum of St. ThereseAbout St. ThereseAbout the Shrine & MuseumUS Shrine & MuseumCanadian ShrineVisiting Lisieux, FrancePlan Your VisitSpecial Events at the ShrineShrine & Museum ToursVisit the Carmelite CampusPilgrimages of FaithPrayer RequestsContact UsDonatePrivacy Policy & Terms of UseTerms of UseUser AgreementThe following are terms of a legal agreement between you and the National Shrine Museum of St. Therese (“Shrine”). By accessing, browsing and/or using this site, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by these terms, as well as the previously stated copyright information, and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations. The Contents of this site are protected by law, including, but not limited to, United States Copyright law and international treaties.Any information that you post on this site will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. You are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from this site any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, or profane material, or any other material that could give rise to any civil or criminal liability under the law. If you do not agree to these terms, do not use this site.This site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties (“External Sites”). You acknowledge that the Shrine is not responsible for the availability of, or the content located on or through, any External Site. You should contact the site administrator for those External Sites if you have any concerns regarding such links or the content located on such External Sites.The Shrine may at any time revise these Terms of Use by updating this posting. By using this site, you agree to be bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to determine the then current Terms of Use to which you are bound.Applicable LawThis site is created and controlled by National Shrine Museum of St. Therese in the State of Illinois, USA. As such, the laws of the State of Illinois will govern these terms and conditions, without giving effect to any principles of conflict of laws. The Shrine reserves the right to make changes to our site and these terms and conditions at any time.Our Address National Shrine Museum of St. Therese 8501 Bailey Road Darien, IL 60561 saint-therese.orgPrivacy PolicyThe National Shrine Museum of St. Therese recognizes that visitors to our website may be concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. Your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy addresses those concerns.Our PolicyThe National Shrine Museum of St. Therese respects the privacy of our online visitors. We do not require you to register or provide personal information to us in order to view our site. We gather personal data, such as names, addresses, zip/postal codes, e-mail addresses, and phone numbers only when voluntarily and knowingly submitted by a visitor.What We Do with the Information We CollectUnless you indicate otherwise when you make your donation, you will occasionally receive postal mailings from us regarding our programs. We will use your e-mail address or phone number only to contact you if we have a question regarding your donation/order. We will use your e-mail address to periodically send you updates only if you have voluntarily opted in to our email newsletter list.E-Mail AddressesEmail addresses are obtained by website visitor opt-in only format. At no time do we ever share your email address with any other organizations, persons, or parties. We do not obtain any email lists from other companies, individuals, organizations, or websites. Individuals may opt-out at any time.Information We Share with OthersWe may periodically share only your name and postal address with other organizations. We are extremely selective in choosing the organizations we associate with in this manner.Your preferences about the Information We CollectIf you prefer that we NOT share any information about you with organizations outside the National Shrine Museum of St. Therese please write to us at National Shrine Museum of St. Therese, 8501 Bailey Road, Darien, IL 60561, call us at 1(800)447-3436 or email us at webmaster@saint-therese.org.Transaction SecurityWe care about the safety and security of your online transaction. When you use a credit card to make a donation at saint-therese.org, your personal credit card information, including your credit card number is encrypted before it travels over the Internet. This technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions, which makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept the credit card information you send to us. Making a credit card donation online at saint-therese.org is just as safe as making a credit card purchase over the telephone. We recognize the importance of respecting the integrity of this material and limit access only to personnel authorized to process your request.Our Use of CookiesDonations to saint-therese.org are possible only if your web browser is set to enable cookies. A “cookie” is a small text file stored and controlled by you personally, on your web browser on your computer’s hard drive. Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal choice. Cookies allow us to understand how you clicked to our site and what pages you click on during your visit to our website. We do not use the cookie to track your activity on sites other than saint-therese.org.Aggregate InformationWe collect non-personal information about how users navigate through our website. We aggregate this statistical information in order to improve our site, and we may share this information with our affiliates or other outside companies. This aggregated information does not include any individual names or personal data, so it does not identify you or any other visitor in any way.Additional InformationOur website has links to others websites whose privacy policies may differ from ours. The National Shrine Museum of St. Therese is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. This policy may be changed or updated from time to time.If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, please write to us at National Shrine Museum of St. Therese, PO Box 1045, Westmont, IL 60559, call us at 1(800) 647-1430 or email us at webmaster@saint-therese.org.Policy updated March 2018.Footer Connect with the ShrineFacebookTwitter We are open 7 days a week 10 AM to 4 PM CT Call: 800-647-1430 for more infoSearch this websiteSign Up for Campus UpdatesWinner of a 2019 Architectural Award for Excellence in Masonry National Shrine of St. Therese is located at 8433 Bailey Road, Darien, IL 60561 National Shrine Museum of St. Therese is located at 8501 Bailey Road, Darien, IL 60561Mass takes place at the National Shrine, Monday through Friday at 11:30 AM.
There is no Mass on weekends.
The Carmelite Campus includes:  National Shrine of St. Therese · Carmelite Spiritual Center · Carmelite Gift Shop · Society of the Little Flower · Order of Carmelites Copyright © 2020 ·
National Shrine and Museum of St. Therese
• Terms of Use and Privacy Policy • Protecting God's Children
